radioandtelly.co.uk 2019-06-06

# Site Terms and Privacy Policy | Radio & Telly UK

## Website Terms and Conditions

By using or contributing to this website, you agree to be bound by the usage terms outlined on this page. We reserve the right to change these terms and conditions from time to time as may be necessary. You should also be aware of this site’s Privacy Policy when using the site.

#### Disclaimer

Content appearing on this site is published in good faith based on personal experiences of the site owners and contributors, information obtained from approved online sources, and information received from visitors to the site. Our aim is to inform visitors by providing access to information not available via other sources. It is not our intention to mislead, offend or upset, and we aim to act quickly to remove misleading, inaccurate or offensive content. Please contact the site administrator if you spot an error, or have an objection to content placed on this site.

Under no circumstances shall the site owners or approved contributors be held liable for any loss or damage caused by reliance on information published on this website.

The site owners/administrators are not responsible for content on sites linked to from this site.

#### Copyright

Material originated by Radio and Telly or its contributors is the copyright of the owners of the radioandtelly.co.uk domain, unless acknowledged otherwise. Copyright ©  radioandtelly.co.uk. All rights reserved.

No part of this website may be copied, mirrored, republished, distributed, or reproduced in any form whatsoever without prior written permission from the site owners.

We acknowledge that in order for us to provide product reviews, on rare occasions content from organisations with which we are affiliated may have been used on this site – it is not our intention to infringe any copyright or trademarks. Logos may be trademarks of other organisations and are acknowledged. In the event that any organisation or individual feels that material used on this site has been used incorrectly or inappropriately on this site, please contact the site’s webmaster and prompt action will be taken.

#### Products, services & offers

This site provides information on a wide range of products and services from a selection of companies. Price, specification and offers relating to products and services promoted are subject to change / withdrawal by these companies at any time, and any purchases made are subject to the terms and conditions of the organisation in question. When placing a purchase as a result of a visit to this or an affiliated site, visitors should always check the official website of the retailer / service provider for full information on price, specification, terms and offers prior to purchase of a product or service.

#### Visitor messages

Visitors to our site are able to post messages via dedicated ‘comments’ pages or in our site forum. Visitors who post messages must not post any material which is false, defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, vulgar, hateful, harassing, obscene, profane, sexually oriented, threatening, invasive of a person’s privacy, or otherwise in violation of ANY law. Legal actions can be taken against anyone posting messages of this sort on this site. Visitors must not post any copyrighted material unless the copyright is owned by them or they have written consent from the owner of the copyrighted material. The site owners reserve the right to edit or delete inappropriate content without prior notice.

Posters remain solely responsible for the content of their messages. The site owners reserve the right to reveal the identity and IP addresses of any poster in the event of a complaint or legal action arising from any content posted.

It is impossible for us to confirm the validity of content submitted by visitors to this site. We do not actively monitor posted messages and are not responsible for their content. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information presented. The messages express the views of the author, not necessarily the views of the site owners/administrators. Anyone who feels that a posted message is objectionable is encouraged to notify the webmaster immediately. We have the right to remove objectionable content within a reasonable timeframe, where we deem that removal is necessary. This is a manual process, however, so please realise that we may not be able to remove or edit particular messages immediately.

We reserve the right to quote and/or re-publish posts made in our forum or our blog. Please see our site’s Privacy Policy regarding messages posted to this site.

#### Site advertising

This site is funded by advertisements. We do not charge visitors for any or our services, nor do we offer any kind of paid subscription service.

As with many websites, we promote a number of selected advertisers using the “affiliate scheme” model. Parts of our site contain banner advertisements and in-content text links to advertisers. This means that, in some cases, a small percentage of any sales generated by our visitors, is apportioned to the site owners to support ongoing site costs.

Where possible, it is our policy to promote products and services only where a member of the Radio and Telly team has experience of using them, but the nature of online contextual advertising means that this is not always possible.

Some of the advertising services used on this site make use of tracking ‘cookies’. For more information on how these may be used, please see our Privacy Policy.

Radio and Telly is a participant in the Amazon Europe S.à r.l. Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising programme designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.co.uk

 **Advertisers:** If you are looking to advertise on this site, note that we normally only consider advertising from companies that are affiliated with one of a number of [affiliate networks](http://www.consumerdeals.co.uk/affiliate.html). We do not accept paid links, and we do not do paid reviews. Note that our audience is predominantly UK-based.

Our Privacy Policy & Cookie Information

## Privacy Policy (Data Protection & GDPR)

We respect your privacy, and do not give or sell any information that you may provide us with to third parties. By using this website, you agree to accept our Privacy Policy.

The site owners have made best endeavors to be compliant with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) which came into force on 25 May 2018.

Be aware that our Privacy Policy may be subject to change. Changes to our Privacy Policy will appear on this web page.

### 1\. Information gathered from visitors

This website does not request or store data deemed to be most sensitive, such as postal addresses and telephone numbers. Additionally, we do not hold financial, payment or medical data. Here is a summary of the data that we collect:

  1. Visitors that wish to interact with our discussion forum will be required to register. Registering results in the visitor’s name, email address, username, encrypted password, date-of-birth and IP address being stored on this site’s web server. Additional information can be entered optionally by the user in the form of a user profile.
  2. Visitors adding comments to site pages or posts will be required to submit their name and email address. These details, together with the IP address will be stored on this site’s web server
  3. An email newsletter service is offered by this site. Should a visitor elect to join the mailing list, their email address, plus email preferences, will be stored on the site’s web server.
  4. In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor’s IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.
  5. Cookies are used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.

The website and associated data is hosted securely on a dedicated server hosted by UK Fast in the UK. The site administrator holds a secure backup for the purposes of disaster recovery.

### 2\. How the Information is used

Data collected /retained on the website is used in the following ways:

  1. Where a visitor posts a page, forum or post comment, the visitor can decide to receive copies of the post and follow-on comments via the supplied email address. Emails include the option to unsubscribe.
  2. Where a visitor elects to opt-in to a newsletter provided by the website, emails will be sent to the supplied email address. Emails include the option to unsubscribe.
  3. Surveys and Polls make use of IP addresses and cookies, to prevent multiple submissions
  4. Server logs and site cookies are used for the purposes of monitoring and improving the performance of our website and service. Cookies enhance the visitor’s experience when using, and some of these cookies are essential to make our site work. We make use of the third-party Google Analytics for site performance and web statistics.

Personal data (such as email addresses) will not be sold, rented or leased to third parties. If requested, we may submit your information to local or government authorities.

### 3\. Visitor Options

If you have subscribed to one of our email lists, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in the email that you receive.

If you have a forum account with us, you can edit or delete data from the “User Control Panel”, or by contacting the Forum Administrator.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings, however this may prevent you from accessing certain features of the website which rely on cookies.

If you wish any personal data that you have submitted to be removed, GDPR legislation allows this, and you should contact the Site Administrator via the [“Contact Us” form](https://www.radioandtelly.co.uk/contact-us.html) found on the home page of this website. Ensure that your message is clearly marked “GDPR Removal Request”.

### 4\. Submitted Content

Where appropriate, and to offer a better service to site visitors, we may republish extracts of the following: emails sent to us, comments made in our discussion forum, comments made to blog posts, social media messages or other messages sent to us electronically. Should we elect to republish content, we will not disclose any user’s email address, telephone number or postal address.

If you do not want us to republish any extracts of correspondence or content submitted to us, then this should be made clear in the body text at the time of submission.

## Cookies

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. They may be used to track your return visits to the website.

Operating costs for running this website are funded by site advertising using affiliate networks. Some advertisement placements on this website make use of third-party cookies from one or more advertising networks. These cookies use anonymous data to improve the advertising experience for visitors, for tracking purposes, and to attribute advertising impressions to this website.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from accessing certain features of the website, such as some forum functionality.

You can find out more about cookies and how to control and delete them here: [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

#### COOKIES USED ON THIS SITE

For your information, here is a summary of the cookies used on this site:

 **Google Analytics**

Our website uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use our site. Google Analytics uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by these cookies about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of our site and to compile statistical reports on website activity.  
We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website. You can find out more information on Google Analytics, and data collected by Google here: [Google Analytics Privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/tos.html)

>  **Google Analytics Cookies: __utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmz and __utmv**

 **Clicky**

Our website uses Clicky to help analyse how users use our site. Clicky is a web analytics platform that provides real-time data to publishers for reporting purposes. The cookies collect the following anonymous information: browser type, exit pages, ISP, language, operating system, page views, referring URL, screen resolution, time/date, pseudonymous IP address. You can find out more information on GetClicky here: [GetClicky Terms](http://getclicky.com/terms)

>  **GetClicky Cookies: __cfduid, cluid, first_pv_ and _jsuid**

 **WordPress**

We make use of the Content Management System WordPress, which collects statistics on visitors. The cookies collect the following anonymous information: browser type, language preferences, referring URL, time/date and pseudonymous IP address. More information here: [automattic.com/privacy](http://automattic.com/privacy/)

 **Our Forum**

When you create an account and log on to our forum, three cookies are created, one for username, one for password and one for your “session”. This. You can find more information on YaBB here: <http://www.yabbforum.com/about.php>

> **YaBB Forum Cookies: __cfduid, cluid, first_pv_ and _jsuid**

 **Twitter Badge**

This site makes use of social networking site Twitter, and some of our pages contain status information using a Twitter Badge Plug-in. This uses cookies to collect the following anonymous information: ad clicks, browser type, mobile carrier, page views, referring URLs, time/date, pseudonymous IP address, search queries, “tweets”, PII (device and application IDs). More information here: [twitter.com/privacy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

 **Facebook**

This site uses social networking tools for Facebook. We use Facebook Connect and Facebook Social Plug-in to offer information about our Facebook followers. This uses cookies to collect the following anonymous information: browser type, location, page views, pseudonymous IP address, “actions taken” . More information here: [www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

#### Cookies: Third Party Advertising

There are costs incurred in hosting an internet website and providing a service to our visitors. Our site, and its affiliated sites make use of on-site advertising to generate revenue to cover our costs. .

Many of the advertising services we use make use of cookies to collect data to ensure that adverts are relevant, and that we receive appropriate recognition for any adverts that we serve to our visitors. In this section, we outline the services that we use, but if you want more information about how advertisers make use of cookies, and your online choices, we recommend you visit the following site: [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices)

 **DoubleClick**

We make use of advertising services operated by Google. Known as DoubleClick DART, this services uses cookies to help target advertising. The cookies collect the following anonymous information: ad serving domains, browser type, demographics, language settings, page views, time/date and pseudonymous IP address. You can find out more, and opt out, at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

 **Criteo**

We make use of advertising services operated by Criteo. Criteo is an advertising network that specializes in retargeting. Criteo’s technology enables advertisers to find potential customers who have left a website and re-engage them through dynamic banner ads generated in real-time. Each ad contains relevant, product specific information determined on a user’s previous visit to an e-commerce site. You can find more information at [www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy](http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy)

>  **Criteo Cookies: oacblock, oaccap, uid, uic, tst, udc, tag, udi, evt, dis, extid and eid**

 **Quantcast**

Quantcast is a service that lets website owners see how many views they get, what age range the people viewing are likely to be in, and what income they are likely to generate. Quantcast is one of the larger audience research and behavioural advertising companies operating, and data from Quantcast is used to better target website advertising. Anonymous data collected includes: browser type, exit page, referring URL, search index and time/date. You can find more information at [www.quantcast.com/docs/display/legal/Privacy+Policy](http://www.quantcast.com/docs/display/legal/Privacy+Policy)

 **Skimlinks**

We use the services provided by Skimlinks on some of our pages. SkimLinks is an affiliate marketing platform that allows website operators such as ourselves to be able to monetise a website through placement of affiliate advertising links. Anonymous data collected includes browser type/ version, device type and pseudonymous IP address. You can find more information on Skimlinks here: [www.skimlinks.com/privacy](http://www.skimlinks.com/privacy)

 **Other Advertising Networks**

  *  **Tradedoubler:** More information on this network at [www.tradedoubler.com/uk-en/legal/privacy.html](http://www.tradedoubler.com/uk-en/legal/privacy.html)
  *  **Affiliate Window:** More information on this network at [www.affiliatewindow.com/documents/Privacy%20Policy.pdf](http://www.affiliatewindow.com/documents/Privacy%20Policy.pdf)

If you have any concerns or questions about this site’s use of cookies, please contact us via the link on our homepage

### Google Advertising

This site displays advertising using the Google advertising network. Third-party vendors including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a visitor’s prior visits to websites that use the network.

Website visitors may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

* * *

Should you have any queries regarding this website’s Privacy Policy, please contact us using our [Contact Us page](https://www.radioandtelly.co.uk/contact-us.html).
